=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 8=
= الحلقة 8 =
(If she wasn't the owner of Sun Group's daughter,)
(إذا لم تكن صاحبة ابنة صن جروب ،)
(I would never date her.)
(لن أواعدها أبدًا.)
(Remove Ren Mingyuan. Confirm) (She's just a burden.)
(أزل Ren Mingyuan. أكد) (إنها مجرد عبء).
Mr. Qian.
السيد تشيان.
It's been a long time.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
Last time, you mentioned getting some clients.
في المرة الأخيرة ، ذكرت الحصول على بعض العملاء.
I have some connections here.
لدي بعض الروابط هنا.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
All of them are high-end clients.
كل منهم من العملاء المتميزين.
Including
مشتمل
the chief director of Miss Beauty.
كبير مديري Miss Beauty.
Miss Beauty.
ملكة جمال الجمال.
This make-up show is very popular.
عرض المكياج هذا يحظى بشعبية كبيرة.
It will be great
سيكون رائعا
if they use our products.
إذا استخدموا منتجاتنا.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
As long as they advertise it in the show,
طالما أنهم يعلنون عنه في العرض ،
your brand, Huarong,
علامتك التجارية ، Huarong ،
will become a hit.
سوف تصبح ضربة.
Mr. Qian,
السيد تشيان ،
regarding the quality of our products,
فيما يتعلق بجودة منتجاتنا ،
I believe you know it very well.
أعتقد أنك تعرفه جيدًا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Of course.
بالطبع.
But Weiyi,
لكن وييي ،
today is the weekend.
اليوم هو عطلة نهاية الأسبوع.
It's my rest day.
إنه يوم راحتي.
I...
أنا...
don't want to talk about work.
لا تريد الحديث عن العمل.
Understand.
يفهم.
Why don't we catch up a little?
لماذا لا نلحق قليلا؟
Here.
هنا.
It's time for us to catch up.
حان الوقت بالنسبة لنا للحاق بالركب.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
I have seen a lot of beautiful saleswomen.
لقد رأيت الكثير من البائعات الجميلات.
But it's my first time meeting
لكنها المرة الأولى التي ألتقي فيها
someone like you
شخص مثلك
who is pretty and stylish.
من هو جميل وأنيق.
I like it.
أحبها.
I'm flattered.
أنا أشعر بالإطراء.
Excuse me. I need to use the restroom.
اعذرني.  أحتاج أن أستخدم دورة المياة.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Shishang Restaurant.
مطعم شيشانج.
That's not far from HB.
هذا ليس بعيدًا عن HB.
Buy me a meal, Weiyi.
اشتري لي وجبة يا ويي.
I'm in the middle of a meeting with a client.
أنا في منتصف اجتماع مع عميل.
Maybe another day.
ربما في يوم آخر.
Client?
عميل؟
I can be your client.
يمكنني أن أكون عميلك.
What kind of clients are you looking for?
ما نوع العملاء الذي تبحث عنه؟
I can introduce them to you.
يمكنني تقديمهم لك.
There's no need.
ليس هناك حاجة.
I can do it myself.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
You are all mine now.
كلك لي الآن.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Bai Zeliu?
باي زيليو؟
Mr. Bai...
السيد باي ...
Mr. Bai, Mr. Bai.
السيد باي ، السيد باي.
I don't know Sun Weiyi is your girl.
لا أعلم أن صن ويي هي فتاتك.
Well, now you know.
حسنا الان تعرف.
But I'm still mad.
لكني ما زلت غاضبة.
Tell me!
أخبرني!
Where did you touch her?
اين لمستها؟
I merely touched her hand.
أنا فقط لمست يدها.
Dai, call the police.
داي ، اتصل بالشرطة.
On it.
عليه.
Bai Zeliu?
باي زيليو؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
We're here for the breeze
نحن هنا من أجل النسيم
so you can wake up.
حتى تستيقظ.
Why are there so many rascals around you?
لماذا يوجد الكثير من الأوغاد من حولك؟
Who are you implying?
من تقصد؟
Your ex-boyfriend
حبيبك السابق
and that ugly businessman.
ورجل الأعمال القبيح.
Bai Zeliu,
باي زيليو ،
this is my choice.
هذا خياري.
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Let me go.
دعني اذهب.
Kiss me then.
قبلني بعد ذلك.
You're crazy.
انت مجنون.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll jump off with you then.
سأقفز معك بعد ذلك.
♪Why is he always the one who makes me feel unsettled?♪
♪ لماذا هو دائمًا الشخص الذي يجعلني أشعر بعدم الاستقرار؟
Fine.
بخير.
You are all right now.
أنت بخير الآن.
♪When he is annoying♪
عندما يكون مزعج
Let me go.
دعني اذهب.
♪Why did my heart beat so fast?♪
♪ لماذا نبض قلبي بهذه السرعة؟ ♪
Weiyi,
وييي ،
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm too worried
أنا قلق للغاية
that's why I lost control.
لهذا فقدت السيطرة.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
are you hungry?
هل انت جوعان؟
Do you want me to get some food with you?
هل تريد مني أن آخذ بعض الطعام معك؟
Looking at your face makes me lose appetite.
النظر إلى وجهك يجعلني أفقد الشهية.
♪I want to go one step further with you♪
♪ أريد أن أخطو خطوة أخرى معك
He probably drugged your wine.
ربما قام بتخدير النبيذ الخاص بك.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
Mr. Qian is not someone like that.
السيد تشيان ليس شخصا من هذا القبيل.
Think of it.
فكر بالأمر.
You can drink a lot.
يمكنك شرب الكثير.
How is it possible for you to be drunk
كيف يمكن أن تكون في حالة سكر
after a few sips?
بعد رشفات قليلة؟
♪If you love me too♪
♪ إذا كنت تحبني أيضًا ♪
It might be I'm on my period.
قد يكون أنا في دورتي الشهرية.
So I'm sleepy.
لذلك أنا نعسان.
♪Don't stand aside and keep quiet♪
♪ لا تقف جانبًا وتلتزم الصمت ♪